Anaro Karo Fabian

Information Communication Technologist/Designer

I am an ICT Personnel/Analyst with wide knowledge in various aspect of Information Communication Technology. 4+ years of experience and highly familiar with a wide variety of computer software's, Hardware engineering, networking, and Windows operating system software's.



Work History

2022-01 -Current

Supply Chain Officer (SAP MM Module)

NNPC Medical Services Limited Benin. 5 Erabor Street, G.R.A. Benin City, Edo State.

Core Responsibilities

(Material Management Module)

- Creation of Purchase Request (PR)
- Creation of Service Order (SO)
- Creation of Local Purchase Order (LPO)
- Creation of Goods Receipt (GR)
- Finding solutions to solving SAP related issues.
- Documents Record Keeping.
- Organizing Departmental Weekly Reports for Management.

2020-03 -2021-01

Operations Manager

S & T Waterfront Resort Center, Ubeji, Delta State.

Core Responsibilities

- Maintaining and Monitoring of Company's Operations.
- Stock level taking.
- Supervising day to day activities.
- Organizing reports for the General Manager.

2019-08 -2020-02

Supervisor (NNPC MPCS)

NNPC Medical Services Ekpan-Warri, Delta State, Warri, Delta State

Core Responsibilities



Personal Info

D.O.B

19th October 1992

L.G.A

Isoko North

Address

9 Steven Ogbonwam Street, Ugbor Village Road, Benin City.

Edo State.

Phone

+2347039226061

+2348154112407

E-mail

anarokarofabian@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com /in/karo-anaro-383b92175



SAP Software

Very Good

Microsoft PowerPoint, Excel and Word

- Regular Inspection of the Bakery Environments.
- Taking records of Bakery Production and distribution.
- Ensure the right Ingredients and chemicals are used properly when mixing.
- Preparing report for the Manager.

2017-11 - Information and Comm. Tech. Personnel (NYSC)

NYSC State Secretariat Jos, Plateau State., Jos, Plateau State

Core Responsibilities

- Registration of corps members.
- Posting of corps members.
- Approval of relocated corps members.
- Secretariat functions (Printing of mails/Copying).
- Graphics Designs for the company. (Flyers, Banners Etc.)

2015-03 - IT Help Desk 2016-02

NNPC Medical Services Ekpan-Warri, Delta State, Warri, Delta State

Core Responsibilities

- · Help Desk.
- Network Troubleshooting.
- Computer System Analyst.
- Hardware Troubleshooting and Repairs.
- Software and Network Administrator.
- Flyer and Banner designs for outreach.

Education

2015-11 - Higher National Diploma: Computer Science

Delta State Polytechnic, Ozoro. - Delta State

2012-11 - Odinary National Diploma: Computer Science

Delta State Polytechnic, Ozoro. - Delta State

Web design

Excellent

HTML

Excellent

JavaScript

Good

UI/UX Design

Excellent

React

Very Good

Nextjs

Very Good

CSS

Excellent

Graphics Design

Excellent

MYSQL

Good

2005-01 - Secondary School Leaving

2011-06 Certificate (WAEC)

Maryland Group of Schools, Warri. - Delta State

1996-01 - Primary School Leaving Certificate

2004-06 Children Foundation Nur/Pri. School, Warri. - Delta State



Certifications

2019-07

Financial Institutions Training Centre (FITC)



Online Research and Learning

Design and Experimenting

Communication and Interaction



Mr. Wilfred Adigwe,
Msc. Computer Science,
Senior Lecturer Computer Science Department,
(Delta State Polytechnic, Ozoro),
+2348034302451.

Engr. Atuegwu E. G(KSP),
Deputy Manager Programming,
PPQC-WRPC-NNPC,
+2348034469166,
atumek224@gmail.com.

Mr. Henry Nwoba,
Supervisor IT.
(NNPC Medical Services Ekpan-Warri),
+2348033102609,
hnwoba@gmail.com.